Blood flows like the tide.
Captain Hook: The Cursed Tides is a adventure, action,
horror film directed by Lars Janssen.
In the aftermath of a devastating defeat by his archnemesis Admiral Smee,
Captain Hook finds refuge in the coastal town of Eldritch Landing.
Admiral Smee, played by Sean Cronin.
Ymirskald, played by Ewen Weatherburn.
Private Turley, played by Cameron Ashplant.
Captain James Hook, played by Richard Rowden.
Akila Blackweather, played by Destiny Viva.
Private Mullins, played by Brandon Ashplant.
Captain Hector Barbossa is a fictional character of the Pirates of the Caribbean franchise,
depicted by Geoffrey Rush and appearing in all five films in the series.
Barbossa debuted in The Curse of the Black Pearl (2003) as the captain of the Black
Pearl and a cursed undead skeleton, where he dies at the end of the film.
However, the character is revealed to have been resurrected by Tia Dalma by the end
of Dead Man's Chest, and has since appeared in an anti-heroic role.
Captain Barbossa was also one of the nine Pirate Lords in At World's End (2007), a privateer in service to King George II and the British Navy while also seeking revenge against
Blackbeard in On Stranger Tides (2011), as well as a rich rogue and influential leader of a prosperous pirate empire and fleet in Dead Men Tell No Tales (2017).
Throughout the series, Barbossa has been conceptualized as a "dark
trickster" and the evil counterpart of Captain Jack Sparrow.
In The Curse of the Black Pearl, it was revealed he was once the first mate of Jack, before he
eventually betrayed him and led a mutiny to take the Black Pearl, becoming Jack's sworn enemy.
However, since At World's End, he and Jack have let
go of their grudge and became allies.
Ever since his appearance, Barbossa has received a highly positive reception by critics, with
praise towards Rush's performance and his interesting rivalry and friendship with Jack.
The film explores themes of island, english
channel, channel islands, hook, guernsey.
The tone is dark.